So what's your plan, Dean?
所以你的计划是什么, Dean?
I mean, after your internship?
我的意思是, 在你实习结束后?
I finish school.
我完成学业.
After school, I look for a job.
完成学业后, 我寻找一份工作.
With your qualifications,
以你的资历,
you won't have much of a problem.
你不会有什么大问题的.
I wish that were true.
我希望那是真的.
Lots of qualified people can't get work.
很多有资格的人找不到工作.
Because businesses can't afford to hire people?
因为企业雇不起人吗?
That's what they say.
那是他们所说的.
Especially with benefits.
尤其带上福利.
So I may not get a job for a long time.
所以我可能不会得到一份工作  很长一段时间里.
And if I can't get a job,
如果我不能得到一份工作.
unemployment must be too high.
失业率必定是过高了.
Of course, I still have to pay off my student loans.
当然, 我仍然必须还清我的学生贷款.
You have to pay for university yourself?
你必须自己支付大学的费用吗?
Doesn't the government subsidize you?
政府不给你补贴吗?
Not much. You're pretty much on your own.
不多. 你大多得靠自己.
Funny how the newspaper headlines start to affect your life.
多有趣啊 报纸头条开始影响你的生活了.
Unemployment, inflation....
失业, 通货膨胀...
Well that's not very cheerful, is it?
Well 那不是很令人愉快, 是吗?
If only the sports pages were better!
要是体育版更好一些该多好!